纳巴  你找到他们的踪迹了吗？
Nabahe, have you found their tracks?
一个女人  一头郊狼朝南边来
There's one woman, one coyote headin' up the south side.
仍然没有他们的踪迹
Still no sign of them.
夏延  他们可能正朝你这边来
Cheyenne, they could be headed your direction.
这里没有他们的踪迹
No sign of them here.
找到了
Got 'em.
峡谷后面八十度
Eighty degrees past the gulch.
找到了
Got them.
是的  他们在跑
Yeah, they're runnin'.
郊狼带着毒品
Coyote's got the pack with drugs.
一个女人在他后面
A woman's behind him.
贩卖人口的人渣
Human trafficking scum!
移动你的方向
Movin' your direction.
雷和我正在行动拦截
Ray and I are on the move to intercept!
停好了  准备好了
Parked and ready.
雷  这边
Ray, this way!
纳巴赫
Nabahe?
纳巴  进来
Nabahe, come in.
纳巴  你要去哪里
Nabahe, where are you headed?
看来他们要去峡谷了
Looks like they're headed for the ravine.
切断他们
Cut 'em off!
他们得让交通部等着
They gotta have transpo waiting.
夏延  去拖车那儿看看  完毕
Cheyenne, go check down by the car trailer, over.
夏延
Cheyenne!
我已经找到了
I already found it.
我们得到了来自西方的消息
We got movement from the west.
快来
Comin' fast.
朝你走  夏延
Heading right for you, Cheyenne.
就位
In position.
快到了
Almost there!
有辆车来了
Got a vehicle incoming.
死人开车
Dead men driving.
我不会来的
Not comin' my way.
可能是毒品拦截
Could it be a drug intercept?
我能看见他们
I can see 'em.
一定是劫机犯
Gotta be a hijacker!
我就在你身边
I'm right here with you.
嘿  别动
Hey, don't move!
-别动  把枪放下  -她是认真的
- Don't move, drop your gun! - She means it!
放下武器
Drop your weapons!
马  过来
Horse, get over here.
我们抓到毒贩抢劫毒贩
We got drug dealers robbin' drug dealers.
在地上
On the ground!
趴下  趴下
Down, down!
-趴下  手举在空中  -趴下
- Get down, hands in the air! - Get down!
-快点  -我说了下来
- Come on! - I said get down!
怎么了
What's happening?
-伙计们  -在地上
- Guys? - On the ground!
趴下  手举在空中
Get down, hands in the air!
我说了下来
I said get down!
趴下  趴下
Get down, down!
郊狼在跑
Coyote's makin' a run for it!
儿子
Son of a...
-趴下  -枪手在山脊上
- Get down! - Shooter's on the ridge!
阻止她
Stop her!
呆在吉普车后面  雷
Stay behind that Jeep, Ray!
马  进来
Horse, come in.
纳巴赫
Nabahe?
伙计们  有人回答我吗
Guys, will someone answer me!
你们还好吧
You guys all right?
-是啊  -是啊
- Yeah! - Yeah!
马  你能看见谁在上面吗
Horse, can you see who's up there?
一定是卡特尔的了望员
Gotta be a cartel lookout.
他们一定是在保护毒品走私
They must be protecting a drug run.
狙击手击毙了拦截
Sniper killed the intercept.
真奇怪
This is really weird!
枪声在山脊上持续200码
Shots keep goin' 200 yards up on the ridge.
没人动  所以趴下
No one's moved, so stay down.
是的  这是个好建议  警长
Yeah, that's good advice there, sheriff.
雷  你能看到那个女人去哪儿了吗
Ray, can you see where that woman's gone?
不  没什么
Nah, nothin'.
我知道这太明显了
I know this is too obvious,
但这是一场真正的墨西哥对峙
but this is a real Mexican standoff.
听着  我们不能就这样被压住了
Look, we can't just stay pinned down like this!
趴下  雷
Get down, Ray!
回来  雷
Get back, Ray.
雷  回来
Ray, get back!
雷
Ray!
该死  雷
Damn it, Ray.
雷  你打中了
Ray, you hit?
不  我只是擦伤了
No, I'm just grazed.
哦  像个婊子一样刺痛
Oh, stings like a bitch.
夏延  你能看见他吗
Cheyenne, can you see him?
妈妈  那是把大枪
Mother, that's a big gun.
她要上吉普车了
She's goin' for the Jeep!
我勒个去
What the hell!
狙击手在逃跑
Sniper's on the run!
马  他太远了
Horse, he's too far away.
我打不中
I can't get a shot.
他很快就要离开你们了
He's heading away from you guys fast,
沿着山脊的南边
down the south side of the ridge.
雷  掩护我们
Ray, cover us!
在上面  头儿
On it, Chief.
是个男人
It's a man.
神圣的迪纳
Holy Dinah.
海洛因  可卡因
Heroin, cocaine.
嘿  这很奇怪  老板  看
Hey, this is strange, boss, look.
是啊  边境上发生了奇怪的事
Yeah, there's weird things happenin' at the border.
越来越奇怪了  老大
It's gettin' a lot weirder, boss.
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell is that?
雷管
Detonator.
好吧  我要这里所有东西的照片
All right, I want pictures of everything here,
尤其是那个引爆器
especially that detonator.
我在华盛顿有人想看这个
I got people in D.C. who wanna see this.
烧掉那些毒品
And burn those drugs!
-祖国呢  证据  -做吧
- What about Homeland, evidence? - Do it!
进来吧
Come in.
先生
Sir.
这是他们寄来的所有东西吗
Is this everything they sent?
是的  你有他们发给你的所有照片
Yes, you have all the photos they've sent you.
我也需要硬拷贝
And I'm gonna need hard copies as well.
好吧  你觉得呢
Okay, what do you think?
肯定是引爆器
It's definitely a detonator,
可能是某种肮脏的炸弹
probably some kind of dirty bomb.
所以  一个ISIS小组正试图
So, an ISIS cell is tryin' to bring...
一个ISIS细胞可能已经在美国建立
An ISIS cell likely already in place in the U.S.
这是某人引爆炸弹的计划
and this is someone's plan to detonate a bomb
一团足以摧毁一座大城市的放射性云
with a radioactive cloud big enough to destroy a major city.
是谁寄来的
Who sent this?
我的一些老朋友
Some old friends of mine.
他们自称为暗狼
They call themselves Shadow Wolves.
肖  我们有个位置
Shaw, we have a location.
朝大理石拱门走去
Head toward Marble Arch.
可汗要派她去开会
Khan is sending her for a meeting.
阿卜杜拉正在行动
Abdula's on the move.
给你坐标  待命
Sending you coordinates, standby.
肖  小心点
Shaw, proceed with caution.
我重复一遍  小心行事
I repeat, proceed with caution.
记住  她是可汗的主要刺客
Remember, she's Khan's main assassin.
超过20人确认死亡
Over 20 confirmed kills.
肖  呆在那儿等支援
Shaw, stay there and wait for backup.
我重复一遍  等待支援
I repeat, wait for backup.
他们在路上
They're on their way.
先生
Sir.
肖  没有后援别进去
Shaw, don't go in there without backup.
肖
Shaw!
你知道我是谁
You know who I am.
告诉我关于可汗的事
Tell me about Khan!
猪
Pig.
可汗呢
Where's Khan?
他已经走了
He's already gone.
他不能就这么做
He can't just do that.
安静的
Quiet!
他在哪里
Where is he?
前往墨西哥
Headed to Mexico.
你杀人的日子结束了
Your days of killing are over.
把你的队伍带到这里来
Get your team here now.
给那个女孩注射吗啡
Stick the girl with morphine.
我还有几个问题要问她
I've got a few more questions for her.
我要提出抗议
I'm filing a protest.
是的  给我打电话
Yeah, CC me on that.
少校  不要进去
Major, do not go in there!
你到底想要什么
What the hell do you want?
很高兴见到你  少校
Nice to see you too, Major.
你知道我在马略卡休假
You know I was on leave in Majorca
在龙舌兰酒的镜头和乳头
up to my eyes in tequila shots and tits.
我以前从没听说过
And I've never heard that before.
来吧
Come on.
你想我了
You've missed me.
自从我们在一起度过那些寒冷的夜晚
Ever since we were stuck together for those freezing nights
在圣彼得堡的安全屋里
in that safe house in St. Petersburg.
只有你的幻想
Only your fantasy.
没有证据
No proof.
他快要出事了
He's on the verge of something.
派别人去
Send someone else.
她今晚会在通布里奇的老狐狸那儿
She'll be at The Old Fox in Tunbridge tonight.
你把她牵扯进来了
You got her involved?
别自以为是
Don't be a presumptuous twit.
她是最好的选择  她想要这份工作
She was the best choice, and she wanted the assignment.
你确定你和她没有联系吗
Are you sure you've had no contact with her?
什么  自从你命令我离开她之后
What, ever since you ordered me to leave her?
你知道我没有
You know I haven't.
这是头等大事
This is top priority.
这次  让我们尽量减少损失
And this time, let's try and minimize the damage,
失去生命  等等
loss of life, et cetera.
影子他  我不相信他
Shadow him, I don't trust him.
你到底在干什么
What the hell do you think you're doing?
我们能聊聊吗
Can we chat?
哦  看在上帝的份上
Oh, for God sake.
米尔顿给了我情报
Milton handed me intel
关于你如何渗透到可汗的行动中
on how you've infiltrated Khan's operation,
他在搞些下流的事
and he's up to something nasty.
去你的
Screw you!
等等  我们做到了
Wait, we did.
多少次
How many times?
我数不清了
I lost count.
就这样
That's it?
两年后
After two years?
你消失了  我不知道你是否死了
You just disappear, I have no clue if you're dead,
现在你出现在这里问我关于可汗的事
and now you show up here asking me about Khan?
是的  很长一段时间也没有你的消息了
Yeah, and nobody's heard from you in a long time, either.
我们没多久
We haven't got long.
他在计划一件大事
He's planning something big.
找到系统室实验室找任何东西
Find System House Labs look for anything
我们的项目叫Tohono
on our project called Tohono.
没能做到
Haven't been able to.
他看得太近了
He's watching me too closely.
他身上有什么东西
Something's just snapped in him,
他离ISIS领导人越来越近了
and he's gotten way closer to ISIS leaders.
你知道  离开这里
You know, just get out of here.
你要揭穿我的伪装
You're gonna blow my cover.
等等  朝我开枪
Wait, shoot at me.
什么
What?
我要跑  你朝我开枪
I'm gonna run and you shoot at me.
还有一件事
One more thing.
一定要错过
Make sure you miss.
你这个混蛋
You wanker!
桑切斯  我不能选择
Sanchez, I can't choose!
我就是不能
I just can't.
你为我选择  桑切斯
You choose for me, Sanchez.
你不好玩
You are no fun.
你以前很有趣
You used to be fun.
吃点这个
Have some of this.
它很精致
It is exquisite.
每瓶由20蒲式耳的梨制成
Each bottle is made out of 20 bushels of pears.
你能相信吗  桑切斯
Can you believe that, Sanchez?
我想去法国
I want to go to France.
我想参观这个葡萄园
I want to visit this vineyard.
我想买这个葡萄园  桑切斯
I want to buy this vineyard, Sanchez.
你觉得他们会卖给我吗
You think they'll sell it to me?
我知道那张脸
I know that face.
我从不喜欢你脸上的表情  桑切斯
I never like that face on you, Sanchez.
你有不好的事情要告诉我  不是吗
You have something bad to tell me, don't you?
我很喜欢这杯白兰地
And I was so enjoying this cognac.
吐出来
Spit it out!
我们昨晚被击中了
We got hit last night.
我们有一次穿越边境
One of our runs across the border.
我们输了多少
How many did we lose?
我们的一只狼被杀了
One of our coyotes was killed.
是谁  伯特伦  赫克托
Who was it, Bertran, Hector?
不确定
Not sure.
没有他们的踪迹
No trace of them.
他们刚刚烧了我们的卡车  还烧了我们的货
They just burned our truck and they burned our load.
狼
Wolves!
Wolves.
去他妈的  伙计
Fuck it, man.
好吧  出来吧
All right, come on out.
噢  楚其
Aw, Chucky.
我告诉过你多少次不要偷偷摸摸的
How many times have I told you not to sneak up
对爸爸那样  嗯
on Daddy like that, huh?
-看起来不错  -哦
- Lookin' good. - Oh.
你知道  你从来都不是个好骗子
You know, you never were a good liar.
看在上帝的份上
For god sakes.
奖励你的辛勤工作
Reward for your hard work.
好吧  孩子们
All right, kids.
我们一起喝吧
Let's jug up.
马  把它带过来
Horse, bring that over here.
味道好极了
Smells great.
是啊  这次你做了什么
Yeah, what did you make this time?
喂  舌兰和马槟榔
Voila, linguine and capers.
是的  你是我唯一认识的全州四分卫
Yeah, you're the only all-state quarterback I know
谁能像这样做饭
who can cook like this.
总有一天你会成为一个真正的好妻子
You're gonna make somebody a real nice wifey someday.
哦
Ooh.
昨天很艰难
Well, yesterday was tough.
很多人甚至为了敌对的卡特尔而杀人
A whole lotta killin' even for rival cartels.
战争每天都在恶化
Wars are gettin' worse every day.
那么  你有没有从你的消息来源
So, did you hear from your sources
华盛顿那些阿拉伯笔记本
in Washington about those Arabic notebooks?
好吧  既然你提到了  我确实收到他们的信
Well, now that you mention it, I did hear from them,
他们给我们派了一个新队员
and they're, sending us a new guy for the team.
为什么  他们认为我们错过了什么
Why, they think we miss something?
不  是
No, it's...
扮演牛仔和印第安人
Play cowboys and Indians?
不  他们想评估一下情况
No, they wanna assess the situation.
哦  我的上帝
Oh my God.
你知道华盛顿现在很疯狂
You know D.C.'s in a frenzy
关于ISIS越境的事
about ISIS crossin' the border.
因为他们已经有了
'Cause they already have.
是的
Yup.
嗯  也许吧
Well, maybe.
但我们在华盛顿还有朋友
But we still have friends in Washington.
我只想说
And I just wanna say that,
你昨天处理自己的方式
the way you handled yourselves yesterday,
我为你感到骄傲
I'm proud of ya.
现在  如果我们能保持清醒
Now, if we can just keep knucklehead
躲在这里
to stay behind cover here.
小弟  你表弟的荣誉仪式这周还在吗
Junior, is your cousin's honor ceremony still this week?
是的  卡洛姆今天早上在做假肢
Yeah, Kallum was up on his prosthetics this morning.
哇  太棒了
Wow, that's awesome.
-哦  对他很好  伙计  -是的
- Oh, good for him, man. - Yeah.
好吧  你知道在那里四次旅行之后  他是我的英雄
Well, you know after four tours over there, he's my hero.
他想加入这个组织
And he wants to join the organization here.
有异议吗
Any objections?
当然不是
Of course not.
莱查姆
L'Chaim.
伙计  我讨厌那边
Man, I hated it over there.
我是说  每条路上都有炸弹
I mean, there's a bomb on every road.
在卡鲁姆没想到的时候打他
Hit Kallum when he didn't expect it.
他们总是这样
They always do.
整个地区一团糟
That whole region is a mess.
伊拉克  伊朗  阿富汗
Iraq, Iran, Afghanistan.
嘿  我们做了我们的工作
Hey, we did our job.
你真的认为军队关心
You really think the military cared
关于我们在那里教他们的
about what we taught them over there?
我是说  你呢
I mean, do you?
追踪老方法有什么用
What's the use in tracking the old ways
当你有一架能做同样事情的无人机
when you got a drone that can do the same thing?
不  是我们带领他们
No, we were the ones that led them
对特定的恐怖组织
to specific terrorist units.
然后他们做了什么
And then what did they do?
好问题
Good question.
你是不是刚按了办公室的某个按钮
Did you just push a button from an office somewhere
砰的一声  到处都是爆炸声
and bam, explosion everywhere.
没错  然后就少了几个恐怖分子
Exactly, and then there's a few less terrorists
把你表兄弟的腿给炸了  什么
to blow your cousins' legs off, what.
我们是他们的恐怖分子
We're their terrorists.
我们是他们眼中的入侵者
We're the invaders in their eyes.
嘿  你表弟做的事很可敬
Hey, what your cousin was doing is honorable.
他在尽自己的职责
He was doing his duty.
就像我们要尽我们的职责一样
Just like we're gonna do our duty.
我们秘密行动
We operate in secret.
但我们的资金是有保障的
But our funding is secure.
就像我常说的
And it's like I always say.
哦  不
Oh, no.
如果一个人独自放屁然后
If a man farts alone and then...
不  不  不  你是说
No, no, no, you mean,
一个自以为屁不臭的人
a man who thinks his farts don't stink...
不  不  如果一个人在森林里放屁
No, no, it's, if a man is in the forest and he farts...
一个在秘密中放屁的人是一个失去了
A man who farts in confidence is a man who has lost...
他的嗅觉
His sense of smell.
-我喜欢这样  -就是这样
- I like that. - That's what it was.
太恶心了
That's so gross.
你为什么要在镜头前打断她的手臂
Why would you break her arm on camera
当你不知道谁在看的时候
when you don't know who's watching?
除了给我惹麻烦
Except to make a shit storm for me?
一次核攻击
One nuclear attack on our soil
所有这些政治正确性都消失了
and all of this political correctness evaporates.
这是一件愚蠢的事
It was a stupid thing to do
这让事情变得非常困难
and it makes things very difficult.
你的意思是你在中间很软
You mean you're gettin' soft in the middle.
我所做的就是为你改变规则
All I do is bend the rules for you
你总是在推动它
and you're always pushing it.
是啊  多年来你的同事一直在开玩笑
Yeah, and for years your colleagues have been holding open
一扇巨大的旋转门喊道  进来攻击我们
a huge revolving door shouting, come on in and attack us.
嗯  这有点过于简单化了
Well, that's a bit of an oversimplification,
但我理解你的沮丧
but I do understand your frustration.
沮丧  现在你甚至在用华盛顿的话来安抚
Frustration, now you're even using D.C. appeasing words.
我派你去做点什么
I'm sending you to do something.
我不知道是什么  但它是开箱即用的
I'm not sure what it is, but it's out of the box.
纳巴  那是什么名字
Nabahe, what the hell kind of a name is that?
我是纳瓦霍人
It's Navajo.
我们一起参加了第一次海湾战争
We were in the first Gulf War together.
看到了一些狗屎
Saw some shit.
他经营一个叫影子狼的单位
He runs a unit called The Shadow Wolves.
是的  我听说过
Yeah, I've heard of 'em.
印度的追踪者用传统的方式抓捕坏人
Indian trackers catchin' bad guys the old fashioned way.
他们很擅长
And they're very good at it.
我以为他们是缉毒局的  贩毒
I thought they were with the DEA, drug trafficking.
预算削减没有让他们关门吗
Didn't budget cuts shut 'em down?
这是一个新的秘密单位  没人知道
This is a new covert unit, nobody knows.
就连波塔克
Even Bor-Tac?
他们在边防战术部门工作
They work with Border Control Tactical,
但我资助他们和我朋友负责是有原因的
but there's a reason I fund them and my friend's in charge.
我是纳巴
It's Nabahe.
所以  你在资助秘密印第安人
So, you're funding covert Indians.
他们找到了带有核弹部件的叙利亚人
They found the Syrian with the nuclear bomb parts.
在德国
In Germany.
纳巴在等你
Nabahe's expecting you.
如果有什么发现你会否认的
And you'll disavow them if something's revealed
或者像你一样暴露
or uncovered just like you would me?
你的飞机在等你
Your plane's waiting.
很抱歉你的人在沙漠里被杀了
I'm sorry your man was killed in the desert
靠那些该死的狼
by those damn wolves.
我不喜欢这种新闻
I don't like this kind of news.
穆罕默德就那样死了
Muhammad dying like that.
我们还应该继续你的计划吗
Should we still move forward with your plan?
我们必须马上去
We must go ahead, immediately.
没有耽搁  我没有时间
No delays, I don't have time.
我知道这个差距
I know this gap.
我知道  它会回来的
I know it, it will come back to me.
劳伦  请进
Lauren, please, come in.
他在这里干什么
What is he doing here?
他让我毛骨悚然
He gives me the creeps.
我也是  事实上  每个人
Me, too, in fact, everyone.
但这就是我让他在身边的原因
But that's why I keep him around.
我一直很担心你
I've been worried about you.
今晚和你搭讪的那个人是谁
Who is the man who accosted you tonight?
我以前见过的足球运动员
A footballer I used to see.
你知道我在你之前和他们约会过  对吧
You know I dated a few of them before you, right?
是的  是的  你做到了
Yes, yes, you did.
但你向他们开枪了吗
But did you shoot guns at them?
当他们想虐待我的时候
When they tried to abuse me.
他一定是为利物浦效力的
He must've played for Liverpool, then.
我不知道你带着它
I didn't know you carry it.
哦  我刚开始
Oh, I just started.
我可以看看这把枪吗
May I see this gun?
当然
Sure.
奥马尔不喜欢枪
Omar doesn't like guns.
他更喜欢其他的防御方法
He prefers other methods of defense.
今天晚上已经过得筋疲力尽了
This evening is now officially past exhausting.
我要睡觉了
I'm going to bed.
你不需要这个
You won't need this here.
尤其是和奥马尔在一起
Especially with Omar around.
你是肖
You Shaw?
是的
Yup.
好吧  进针迪克  我们走
Well, get in needle dick, let's go.
抓住你的短裤
Hang on to your shorts.
欢迎来到我们的高科技T恤
Well, welcome to our high tech teepee.
这一切都是你制造的
You built this all under the radar?
是的  在你老板的帮助下
Yeah, with the help of your boss
但你不能告诉任何人
but you can't tell anybody.
布兰森会在你来之前给我头皮
Branson will scalp me before you can?
嘿  各位  听着
Hey, everybody, listen up!
这是我们的新人
Here's our newbie.
我看他不像印度人
He don't look Indian to me.
是的  他也没有
Yeah, well, he doesn't either.
他有一部分是日本人
He's part Japanese.
战后他祖父驻扎在东京
His grandfather was stationed in Tokyo after the war.
是的  我们称他为我们的本土武士
Yeah, we call him our native samurai.
我也是混血儿  法国妈妈
I'm a half-breed also, French mother.
哦  凯瑟琳·德纳芙
Ooh, Catherine Deneuve.
我敢打赌他来自那个部落
I bet he's from that one tribe,
什么是著名的部落
what's the famous tribe?
-哦  -想要的部落
- Ooh! - The Wannabe tribe.
-想要的部落  -是的
- The Wannabe tribe. - Yeah.
就是那个
That's the one.
你什么都没有
So, what, you got nothin'?
我不知道有这样的事
I didn't realize there was such a thing
作为一只母影狼
as a female Shadow Wolf.
哦  他们是最凶残的一类  兄弟
Oh, they're the most ferocious kind, brother.
她有爪子
And she's got claws.
她的咬法呢
And her bite?
比她的吠声还糟
It's worse than her bark.
所以呢
So?
你打算怎么办
What are you gonna do?
你要加入我们吗
Are you gonna join us?
还是你要跑
Or you gonna run?
你知道  我不确定
You know, I'm not sure.
但我会告诉你我会做什么  我会向你学习的
But I'll tell you what I will do, is I'll learn from you.
因为我今天早上听到的一个故事
Because of a story I heard this morning.
关于他
About him.
关于在某个被遗弃的村庄
About bein' in some godforsaken village
在海湾战争期间的伊拉克
in Iraq during the Gulf War.
他一浪接一浪地拖延
He held off wave after wave
萨达姆的共和国卫队拯救了他的部队和我的老板
of Saddam's Republican Guards saving his unit and my boss.
只是当地的民间传说
Just native folklore.
不是为了我老板
Not for my boss.
我妈妈身上有切诺基
My mother has some Cherokee in her.
这算不算
Does that count?
哦  伙计
Oh, man.
每个人都有切诺基
Everybody got Cherokee in them.
甚至约翰尼·德普
Even Johnny Depp.
哦  现在有一个真正的印第安人
Ooh, now there's a real Indian.
Pshh
Pshh.
在我看来你不像强尼·德普
You don't look like no Johnny Depp to me.
14天
14 days.
那是我剩下的大部分时间了
That's the most time I have left.
我的实验室只能发现如何杀人
My lab can only discover how to kill,
但不是如何治愈
but not how to heal.
帐号在里面
Account numbers are in there.
处理好所有的债务
Take care of all debts.
让华盛顿的人付出高昂的代价
And make the man in D.C. pay dearly.
希望她从未出生
And make her wish she had never been born.
你飞往墨西哥的班机是什么时候
When's your flight to Mexico?
米尔顿十点钟来找我
Milton's got me on 10 o'clock.
她打电话  你就跳
She calls, you jump.
我们不都是吗
Don't we all?
我有两个最好的探员在追踪可汗
I have my two best agents tracking Khan.
是的  米尔顿女士  我明白
Yes, Lady Milton, I understand.
这需要一些时间
It will take some time.
是的  我会联系的  谢谢
That's right, I will be in touch, thank you.
嗯  你把肖送到边境的预感是对的
Well, your hunch to send Shaw to the border was right.
但他找到可汗的可能性有多大
But what are the odds of him actually finding Khan?
他们不好
They're not good.
冰上巡逻队和边境巡逻队竭尽全力
ICE and Border Patrol do the best they can
资源有限  但他们的手是绑着的
with limited resources, but their hands are tied.
可汗不会是唯一一个通过的人
And Khan won't be the only one getting across.
去年有成千上万的叙利亚人越境
Thousands of Syrians crossed last year.
谁知道其中有多少是伊斯兰国
Who knows how many of them are ISIS?
但是  先生  审查程序
But, Sir, the vetting process.
审查过程是假新闻
The vetting process is fake news.
胡说
It's bullshit!
谁知道有多少人可以转身或已经转身
Who knows how many could turn or have already turned?
先生
Sir?
我很担心你
I'm worried about you.
我知道你女儿被杀时发生了什么
I understand what happened when your daughter was killed
在阿富汗  但我相信你在行动
in Afghanistan, but I believe that you are operating
从报复的角度坦白地说
from a position of revenge and frankly,
你违反了很多规定
you are breaking so many rules
它不仅提醒我  它
that it not only alarms me, it...
去完成这个想法吧
Go ahead and finish the thought.
先生  请听我说
Sir, please listen to me.
不  听我说  因为我只想说一次
No, listen to me, because I'm only gonna say this once.
你不懂得珍惜
You have no appreciation for the significance
我们现在的战斗
of the fight that we're in.
美国也犯了很多同样的错误
The U.S. is making the same mistakes so many others have.
你这一代人不懂历史  所以你不知道
Your generation doesn't read history, so you have no clue
我们正在重温威尔逊的绥靖错误
that we're reliving the appeasement mistakes of Wilson,
在张伯伦的包围下跌跌撞撞地进入我们自己的维也纳
of Chamberlain, and stumbling into our own siege of Vienna.
这是正确的
That's right.
向我摇头
Shake your head at me
因为我不知道我在说什么
because I don't know what I'm talking about!
你不会读ISIS社交媒体的每日新闻简报
You don't read the daily ISIS social media press briefings.
在海滩上斩首数十人
Beheadings of dozens on a beach,
把男人和女人活活烧死在笼子里
burning men and women alive in cages,
我们应该什么都不做
and we're supposed to do nothing?
还有一些她训练的胆小鬼士兵
And some chicken-shit soldier that she was training,
她帮助过上更好的生活
who she was helping to lead a better life,
他把枪对着她喷
he turns his gun on her and sprays her
面对子弹说：  上帝是伟大的
in the face with bullets and says, "God is great."
先生  对不起
Sir, I'm sorry...
走出
Get out!
所以你只能在街上闲逛
So you're just gonna roam the streets
墨西哥敲毒品贩子的门
of Mexico knocking drug dealers' doors?
差不多吧
Something like that.
目标
Goal!
一定是我最想念你的一件事
Has to be one of the things I missed about you most.
别害怕
No fear.
你错了
You're wrong.
我有很多恐惧
I've got plenty of fear.
但我有一个密码
But I got one code.
我知道  拥抱它
I know, embrace it.
等等  我有东西给你
Wait, I have something for you.
试试这个  史迪尔顿
Try this, Stilton.
就在你妈妈的路上
Made just down the road from your mum.
那么  可汗想要什么
So, what's got Khan wanting
把脏弹偷偷带进美国
to sneak a dirty bomb into the U.S.?
好吧  他资助恐怖袭击已经很多年了
Well, he's been financing terrorist attacks for years.
你知道的
And you know this
因为米尔顿让你跟着钱走
because Milton has you following the money?
我从来不知道我的LSE学位会把我带到这样的高度
I never knew my LSE degree would take me to such heights.
我以前离他比较近  但现在我只是个眼红
I used to be closer to him, but I'm just eye candy now.
我们好几个月没睡过了
We haven't slept together for months.
他有点不对劲
And there's something really wrong with him,
某种疾病
some kind of sickness.
他什么都不告诉我
He won't tell me a thing.
你认为这就是他现在的动力
And you think that's what's driving him now?
在美国边境和伊斯兰国做点什么
Into doing something with ISIS on the U.S. border?
也许 吧
Maybe.
最后一次为家人报仇的机会
A last chance to avenge his family.
他们来自阿富汗
They come from Afghanistan.
嗯  我应该说他们来了
Well, I should say they came.
美军歼灭了其中大部分
U.S. military annihilated most of them.
跟踪他到他家的村庄
Tracked him to his family's village,
叫了无人机  所有人都被消灭了
called in drones, everyone wiped out.
他的侄女  侄子  表亲  但他都不在
His nieces, nephews, cousins, but he wasn't even there.
我们成了高科技野人
We've become high tech savages.
奥马尔  你是什么
Omar, what are you...
看  这里都是郊狼的踪迹
See, these are all the coyote trails here.
你接到布兰森的电话
You got a call, from Branson.
嘿  夏安  让他起来  在你桌边
Hey, Cheyenne, et him up, at your desk.
你好
Hello?
所以  你叫夏延  但你是纳瓦霍人
So, your name's Cheyenne but you're Navajo.
是的  那是雷诺
Yeah, and that's Reynaro.
他甚至不是意大利人
He's not even Italian.
什么  你在跟我说话吗
What, are you talkin' to me?
不  你在和我说话
No, you talkin' to me?
你在和我说话吗
Are you talkin' to me?
别诋毁唯一伟大的涅罗
Stop defaming the only great Niro.
哦  那是个帅哥
Oh, that's a good looking guy.
那是你男朋友吗
Is that your boyfriend?
那是怪物杀手
That's the monster slayer.
是纳瓦霍人的灵魂
It's a Navajo spirit?
杀害异神的人
The slayer of strange gods.
听起来像我的工作描述
Sounds like my job description.
好吧  现在你完蛋了
Well, now you're screwed.
我不能说我以前没听说过
I can't say I haven't heard that before.
不是  我是认真的
No, I'm serious.
他会来找你的
He will come for you.
当他这么做的时候  你就逃不掉了
And when he does, you won't escape.
那是你们民族的传说吗
Is that one of your peoples' legends?
什么人
What people?
你在说谁
Who are you talkin' about?
有珠子的那个
The ones with the beads?
地毯呢
And the rugs?
那些人
Those people?
你知道我的意思
You know what I meant.
不  我不知道你是什么意思
No, I don't know what you meant.
你为什么不告诉我
Why don't you tell me?
你到底把我弄进什么鬼地方了
What the hell have you gotten me into?
这是怎么一回事
What is it?
我问纳巴赫发生了什么事
I asked Nabahe what was goin' on.
他告诉我鸟的羽毛保护它
He told me that the feathers of a bird protect it
冬天的霜冻
from the frosts of the winter.
是的  那是他最喜欢的
Yeah, that's one of his favorites.
是的  他好像有很多
Yeah, he seems to have a lot of 'em.
我刚传给他的情报
The intel I just passed to him
来自可靠的英国消息来源
is from a reliable British source.
Monte Rey外面的Menendez卡特尔正在帮助伊斯兰国营地
The Menendez Cartel outside Monte Rey are aiding ISIS camps
靠近墨西哥边境
near the Mexican border.
Nabahe会让你掩护小径
Nabahe's gonna have you cover the trails
他知道他们的狼用的
that he knows their coyotes use.
是的  我今晚要和他出去
Yeah, well, I'm goin' out with him tonight.
肖  只要给我找点看得见的东西
Shaw, just find me something tangible,
信号或可靠的人类情报
signal or reliable human intel.
我一分钱也拿不到
I can't get a dime out of anyone here,
尤其是对于一些隐蔽的东西
especially for something covert,
除非我有具体的东西
unless I have something concrete.
是啊  也许一个孤独的战士可以造成更多的伤害
Yeah, well maybe a lone warrior can do more damage
比整个军队在陌生的地方
than an entire army in unfamiliar territory.
我没听说过那个
I haven't heard that one.
从一个饼干盒里
From a Cracker Jack box.
我10岁  它对我说
I was 10, it spoke to me.
走吧
Just go.
所以  我老板出城了
So, my boss is out of town.
我在经营这个地方
I'm running this place.
这种方式
This way.
噢  要是我有枪就好了  你这个小混蛋
Oh, if only I had my rifle, you little rat bastard.
这是一大笔钱
This is a lot of money.
是的  是的
Yes, it is.
但你很狡猾
But you are a tricky one.
所以  是什么阻止了我杀了你
So, what's stopping me from killing you
把这些都留着  嗯
and keeping all this, eh?
我刚刚杀了她
I just had her killed.
因为背叛了我
For betraying me.
我认为你把我当成敌人是愚蠢的
I think you would be foolish to make me your enemy.
你看起来不像个傻瓜
You don't look like a fool.
不
No.
我还需要你小心这个英国人
I also need you to watch out for this Brit,
你怎么说的  暴徒
how you say it, thug.
你想什么时候离开
When do you want to leave?
明晚
Tomorrow night.
你的人在那里见你
And your men are meeting you there?
我什么时候告诉他们
I'll let them know when.
我不想要像上次那样的惊喜
I don't want any surprises like last time.
那不会发生的
That won't happen.
但是那些狼  我不能保证
But those wolves, I can't guarantee.
别担心他们
Don't worry about them.
我有他们的计划
I have plans for them.
哦  别惹她
Oh, don't mess with her.
她是个卑鄙的人  嗯
She's a mean one, eh?
刺客
Assassin.
你知道吗
You know what?
你需要让你的灵魂安静下来
You need to quiet your soul.
你真的变成了一个和大自然在一起的人  嗯
You really become one with nature out here, huh?
哦  你在这里看到很多奇怪的东西
Oh, you see a lotta weird things out here.
让你们城里人跑回去
Make you city people run back
去你的公寓和购物中心
to your condos and your shoppin' malls.
你在这里见过最奇怪的事是什么
What's the strangest thing you've ever seen out here?
什么  在你身边
What, beside you?
大约一周前我们
About a week ago we were
看着一条路  就在那山脊上
lookin' at a path up there, just over that ridge,
看到了这个小小的红灯  这个小小的红点
and saw this little red light, this little red dot.
激光
Laser.
不  只是一个红点  然后它就开了
No, it was just a red dot, and then it went zip!
在这里大约200码然后这个
Over here about 200 yards and then this
闻  这臭味  腐烂  然后这个
smell, this stench, rotten, and then this
笑  这奇怪的笑声
laugh, this weird cackle,
我不知道是什么  然后不知从哪里冒出来
I don't know what it was, and then out of nowhere.
我对你很好  不是吗
I got ya pretty good, didn't I?
很有趣
Very funny.
那味道呢
What about the smell?
嗯  那部分是真的
Well, that part's true.
有时我们能抓住别人只是因为你能闻到他们
Sometimes we can catch people just 'cause you can smell 'em,
有时半英里外
sometimes half a mile away.
你现在闻到什么了吗
Do you smell something now?
是啊  你吃了太多玉米煎饼了
Yeah, you been eatin' too many burritos.
别碰豆子  好吗
Stay away from the beans, will ya?
最难闻的气味是恐惧
The worst smell is fear.
你也能闻到内疚的味道
You can smell guilt, too.
从你的毛孔里出来
Comes outta your pores.
在那边的小路上
Up the path over there.
郊狼带头
Coyotes leadin'.
看起来像四个人
It looks like four people.
去找马和夏延
Go find Horse and Cheyenne.
趴下  趴下  趴下  趴下
Get down, get down, get down, get down!
别动  别动
Don't move, don't move!
-别动  -趴下
- Don't move! - Get down!
趴下  趴下
Get down, get down.
-趴下  -在地上  现在
- Get down. - On the ground, now!
这些都不是可汗
None of these are Khan.
不
No!
趴下  趴下
Get down, get down.
-嘿  嘿  -趴下  趴下
- Hey, hey! - Stay down, stay down!
嘿  回来  下来
Hey, get back here, get down!
趴下  趴下
Stay down, stay down!
-在地上  在地上  嘿  -在地上
- On the ground! On the ground, hey! - On the ground.
夏延  掩护他们
Cheyenne, keep 'em covered.
回来  嘿
Get back here, hey!
他到底去哪了  马
Where the hell did he go, Horse?
我们永远找不到他
We're never gonna find him.
郊狼就这样消失了
Out here coyotes can disappear just like that.
到那边去
Get over there.
那女孩会怎么样
What'll happen to the girl?
可能会把她卖给性交易
Probably gonna sell her to the sex trade.
狼会以这种或那种方式赚钱的
The coyote's gonna make his money one way or another.
不
No!
怪物杀手  纳瓦霍精灵
Monster slayer, Navajo spirit.
他是异神的杀手
He's the slayer of strange gods.
他会来找你的
He will come for you.
当他这么做的时候  你就逃不掉了
And when he does, you won't escape.
肖
Shaw!
埃里克
Eric!
你看到凶手了吗
You saw the slayer?
在夏安打电话给你之前你不会回来找我们的
You wouldn't come back to us until Cheyenne called to you.
来吧  我有个地方让你睡
Come on, I got a place for you to bunk.
好
Well?
不
No!
为什么我们不能打电话到国土局
Why can't we just call in Homeland?
-有无人驾驶飞机在沙漠边界搜索吗  -因为他们什么都不会做
- Have drones search the desert border? - Because they won't do anything.
他们会监听无辜者的电话
They'll listen in on innocent peoples' phone calls,
他们会看每封该死的邮件
they'll read every goddamn email,
但要他们监视边境
but ask them for surveillance on the border,
而且  哦  不  我们不能那样做
and it's, oh, no, we can't do that.
但我和祖国有联系
But I have a connection at Homeland
他欠我一个人情
and he owes me a favor.
你要告诉他们什么
What are you gonna tell them?
哦  我知道会有坏事发生吗
Oh, I know something bad is gonna happen?
亚历克斯  他们告诉他们的时候没有听沙特的
Alex, they didn't listen to the Saudis when they told them
关于车臣轰炸机炸毁波士顿马拉松
about the Chechen bomber blowing up the Boston Marathon,
但他们会听你的
but they'll listen to you.
请原谅我
Excuse me.
关上门
Close the door.
刚好赶上
Just in time.
为了什么
For?
我在这里一事无成
I'm getting nowhere here.
你的经纪人是我们最好的机会
Your agent is the best chance we have.
我需要你推他
I need you to push him.
到底要做什么
To do what, exactly?
我们需要找到可汗
We need to find Khan.
我看看我能做什么
I'll see what I can do.
迈凯轮的最新消息是什么
What's the latest on McLaren?
他核实了可汗在墨西哥的情况
He verified Khan's in Mexico.
你现在应该去那里
You should head there now.
在他再次起诉之前
Before he just charges in again?
不幸的是  这就是他
Unfortunately, it's what makes him
如此有效和破坏性
so effective and destructive.
就像我认识的所有男人一样
Like all the men I know.
第一个女人
The first woman
领导这个地方被称为家庭主妇间谍
to lead this place was called the housewife spy.
她经历了地狱
She went through hell.
试图控制但丁的9度
Trying to contain Dante's nine degrees?
是的
Yup.
我把他留在那里是为了提醒自己
I keep him there to remind myself
我们面对的是同一个地狱
that we're dealing with the same hell,
只是不同的魔鬼
just different devils.
白宫
White House.
我要和莱恩·布莱克谈谈
I need to speak to Ryan Blake.
亚历克斯  怎么了
Alex, what's up?
布兰森和米-6有点关系
Branson is up to something with MI-6.
快过来
Come over now.
你是真的吗
Are you real?
你是吗
Are you?
这是个好问题
That's a good question.
楚其  别管他
Chucky, leave him alone!
你睡在我房间里
You slept in my room.
是 啊
Yeah.
想看魔术吗
Wanna see a magic trick?
可以
Okay.
肖  听到了吗
Shaw, you hear me?
是的
I did.
前进
Go ahead.
为了我
For me?
现在吃你的薄煎饼
Now eat your damn pancakes.
我们得走了
We gotta go.
谢谢您
Thank you.
拜托  你不能逃跑
Come on, you're not escaping.
嗨  嗨  伙计们
Hi, hi, guys.
这是朱尼尔的姑妈  卡伦的妈妈
So, this is Junior's aunt, Kallum's mom.
你一定很骄傲
You must be very proud.
这是他们的祖父
And this is their grandfather.
那是谁
Who's that?
哦  那是娜塔妮  娜芭的哥哥
Oh, that's Natanni, Nabahe's brother.
他是一个光荣的战争英雄
He's a decorated war hero.
海豹突击队六队
SEAL Team Six?
他们很多年没说话了
They haven't spoken in many years.
是的  发生了一些非常糟糕的事情
Yeah, something, something really bad happened
在他们之间  他们只是没有
between them and they just don't.
娜塔妮
Na-tan-ee?
你们白人就是这么说的
That's the way you white people would say it.
不是阿尼  是指领袖
Not-ah-nee, it means leader.
来吧  孩子们  帮我一把
Come on, boys, give me a hand here.
你走的是我们祖先的路
You followed the path of our ancestors.
你为拯救我们的土地而战斗
You fought to save our land.
我为你骄傲  儿子
I'm proud of you, son.
我想让你加入这个团队
I want you to join the team.
敬礼
Salute!
什么  你以为我不知道你要来
What, you didn't think I knew you were coming?
你有一些严重的问题
You've got some serious issues.
是的  告诉我
Yeah, tell me about it.
你知道他刚跟我们说了什么吗
You know what he just told us?
可汗在美国已经有两个情报局的小组了
That Khan has two ISIS cells already here, in the U.S.,
他们已经等了好几个月了
and they've been waiting for 'em for months.
我告诉过你我不会站着
And I told you I will not stand
为了这些审讯
for these kinds of interrogations.
亚历克斯  没时间了
Alex, there isn't time.
我们没有钱让他成为我们的朋友
We don't have the luxury to make him our friend
帮助他认清自己的错误
and help him see the error of his ways.
如果他只是对你撒谎呢
And what if he just lied to you?
只是让你停下来
Just to get you to stop?
你想冒这个险吗
And you wanna take that chance?
如果他说的是实话我们就错失了机会
That if he's telling the truth we miss the opportunity
阻止袭击
to stop an attack?
没人会在乎我们是怎么得到这些信息的
Nobody's gonna care how we got the information
如果我们能阻止这一切
if we can stop this.
这不是一场公平的战斗
It's not a fair fight.
你不明白
You don't get it.
就这么简单
It's that simple.
仪式到了吗
Ceremony get to you?
我什么都有
Everything's got to me.
你看到讽刺了吗
You do see the irony?
什么
What?
你的人  有珠子的人
Your people, the ones with the beads?
还有那些有着悠久历史的
But also the ones that have a long-standing history
为这个国家的军队服务
of serving this country's military.
正是军队把他们赶出了自己的土地
The very army that ran them off their lands,
屠宰和散播
slaughtering and scattering them
从一个地方到另一个地方
from one hellhole of a reservation to the next.
纳巴有句话
Nabahe has a saying.
你的意思是    一切都有联系吗
You mean, "All is connected?"
是的  那个
Yeah, that one.
但他还有一个
But he has another one.
每一代人都为下一代做出牺牲
"Each generation sacrifices for the next."
联系就是牺牲
The connection is the sacrifice.
他在对面
He's across.
我把他留在华雷斯那家被烧毁的工厂
I left him in that burnt factory in Juarez
和他那种人在一起
with some of his kind.
还有一件事  对任何人都一言不发  嗯
And another thing, not a word to anyone, eh?
老板永远不会知道
The boss can never know.
我能从这里闻到你的臭屁股  朋友
I can smell your stinky ass from here, amigo.
垃圾车在拖车上
Dirt bike's on the trailer.
你知道他在哪吗
You know where he is?
嗯  我有一件事是肯定的
Well, I know one thing for sure.
朱尼尔  拿了我的麦克风吗
Junior, got my mic?
你的老板总是善于获取情报
Your boss is always good at getting intel.
麦克风系统准备好了
Mic system's up and ready.
不远处是一家废弃的工厂
It's an abandoned factory not far away.
小家伙  马甲
Junior, vest!
叫Bor Tac来  边境巡逻队
Call in Bor-Tac, Border Patrol?
雷  拿点45和箱子
Ray, take the .45 and the case.
还没有
Not yet.
枪上了子弹
Guns are loaded.
听着  我不会冒着被人骂的风险
Listen, I'm not gonna risk getting crap
为了一些英国人的预感
for some Brit's hunch.
我给肖买了件背心
I got a vest for Shaw.
快点  我们走
Come on, let's go!
你刚刚受洗
You have just been baptized
带着桑切斯的尿  我的朋友
with Sanchez's piss, my friend.
没什么
That's nothing.
在伊拉克沙漠里喝了我自己的尿
Drank my own piss in the Iraqi desert
为了活两个星期
for two weeks to stay alive.
真恶心
That is disgusting.
但你是个年轻的强壮的男孩  哈
But you are a young strapping, tough boy, huh?
不  只有英国人
No, just British.
哦  谢谢你帮我穿好衣服
Oh, thanks for gettin' dressed up for me.
不客气
You're welcome.
事实上  我要谢谢你
In fact, I have you to thank,
因为我在主持一个募捐活动
because I am hosting a fundraiser
为了死去的英国间谍的家人
for the families of dead English spy.
你想来我的国家干什么
What do you want coming here to my country?
听着  我不在乎你卖毒品
Listen, I don't care about you sellin' drugs
对于愚蠢的美国孩子
to stupid American kids,
但你知道你在和伊斯兰国的混蛋做交易
but you do understand you're makin' deals with ISIS bastards
他们要炸掉那些顾客
who are gonna blow up those same customers,
越境走私恐怖分子
smuggling nasty terrorists across the border
只是为了摧毁你们的市场
just to destroy your markets.
我是说  你有多蠢
I mean, how stupid are you?
他到底在说什么
What the hell is he talkin' about?
他神志不清
He's delirious.
桑切斯
Sanchez?
哦  伙计
Oh, mate!
我觉得议会很狡猾
And I thought Parliament was devious.
如果我是你  我会照顾你的  朋友
I'd watch your back if I was you, amigo.
胡说  杰菲
Nonsense, jefe!
我会把他的头砍下来寄给他的
I'll cut his head off and send it to his...
死去的顾客不给我付账单
Dead customers don't pay my bills.
既然你很喜欢
And since you like it so much,
我们会为你的午餐提供更多的小便
we will provide some more piss for your lunch.
给我们一个你的冠冕
Just give us one of your Coronas.
味道差不多
It tastes about the same.
是啊  你是
Yeah, well, you are a...
你的英语怎么说
How do you English say?
你是个厚脸皮的家伙
You are a cheeky fellow.
我敢打赌你的头会成为一个好足球
Bet your head would make a good football
我们周六的比赛
for our Saturday game.
快把他弄出去
Get him out of here, now!
带他去仓库
Take him to the warehouse!
有什么事吗
Anything?
什么都没有
There's nothing.
伙计  我讨厌这部分
Man, I hate this part.
等待
The waiting.
我们在等什么
We're waiting for what?
他们在里面
They're in there.
他们在坐鸭子
They're sittin' ducks!
朱尼尔  有什么事吗
Junior, anything?
娜达
Nada.
小费不好
A bad tip?
嗯  有时候你得等
Well, sometimes you just gotta wait.
当你猎杀响尾蛇的时候
Figure when you're huntin' rattlesnakes...
小心  他们先咬你
Beware, they bite you first.
哦  你到底在这里干什么
Oh, what the hell are you doin' here?
她让你跟着我  不是吗
She's got you followin' me, hasn't she?
离他们来还有一分钟
We got about a minute until they get here!
也许更少
Maybe less.
抓住迈凯轮  我们离开这里
Get McLaren, let's get outta here!
迈凯轮  我们得走了
McLaren, we gotta go!
快点
Come on!
我要杀了你
I'm going to kill you!
不能失去你  少校
Can't afford to lose you, Major.
至少现在还没有
Not yet, at least.
另外  我有个情况
Plus, I have a situation
这需要你的专业知识
that needs your particular expertise.
我知道他们在里面
I know they're in there!
我知道他们在里面  我能感觉到
I know they're in there, I can feel it.
坐着别动  雷
Sit still, Ray.
但他们在里面  我们现在就要抓住他们
But they're in there and we need to get 'em now!
我觉得有些东西动了
I think something moved.
远西区
Far west end.
有人在下面
Somebody's down there.
是的  他们在里面
Yeah, they're in there.
我知道是的
I know they are.
我们现在得把这些人带走
We gotta take these guys now.
你不知道  雷
You don't know that, Ray.
别动
Just hold still.
别动  开玩笑吧
Hold still, are you kidding me?
我们在这里等什么
What are we waiting for in here?
告诉雷保持冷静
Just tell Ray to stay calm.
什么都没动
Nothing's moved.
等等  看
Wait, look!
西北角
Northwest corner.
我看到了
I see 'em.
他们在那里
They're there.
是的  该死的  他们在里面
Yeah, damn right they're in there.
雷  你到底在干什么  ?
Ray, what the hell are you doing!?
雷  你会被狠狠揍一顿的
Ray, you're gonna get a hell of a beatin'
当这一切结束
when this is over.
好吧  来吧
All right, hit it.
嘿  雷  回来
Hey, Ray, get back in here!
该死的  雷  我说了退后
Damn it, Ray, I said stand down.
雷  回来
Ray, get back in here!
肖  掩护那个笨蛋
Shaw, cover that fool's ass.
想自杀吗
Tryin' to get yourself killed?
不  我要往南走
No, I'm goin' south.
现在  看着我的六个
Now, watch my six.
-我在跟踪吗  -是的  跟着他
- Am I followin'? - Yeah, follow him!
倒霉
Shit.
雷  别出去
Ray, don't go out there!
就在下面  等等
Just about down there, hold on!
雷
Ray!
上帝啊
Jesus.
性交
Fuck!
快点  快点
Come on, come on!
朱尼尔  把车开到下面去
Junior, get the van down there now.
在仓库等我
Meet me up at the warehouse.
雷倒下了  他打了三下
Ray's down, he took three hits.
该死的  雷
God damn it, Ray.
马  马  回来
Horse, Horse, get back here!
回来帮我对付雷
Get back here and help me with Ray.
现在
Now!
其中一个正在往里走
One of them's heading inside.
夏延  有他的踪迹吗
Cheyenne, is there any sign of him?
那一枪肯定死了
The one Horse shot is definitely dead.
让雷准备好行动
Get Ray ready to move.
我受到了攻击
I'm under fire!
-来吧  -马  马  给我们掩护
- Come on. - Horse, Horse, give us cover!
-来吧  -我们走吧
- Come on. - Let's go!
马  快上去  退后夏延
Horse, get up there and back up Cheyenne!
她在生火
She's takin' fire.
雷  看着我  雷
Ray, look at me, Ray!
肖
Shaw!
抓住那个混蛋
Get the bastard.
从我的亚视上下来
Get off my ATV.
再来一个
One more down.
快点  醒醒
Come on, wake up.
好吧  你真幸运  孩子
Well, you're one lucky SOB, son.
你能上货车吗
Can you make it to the van?
是 啊
Yeah.
这不是可汗  他在哪里
This isn't Khan, so where is he?
我开枪的不是可汗
The one I shot wasn't Khan.
雷
Ray?
他走了
He's gone.
我不能把他带回来
I couldn't bring him back.
哦  雷
Oh, Ray.
你这个该死的傻瓜
You damn fool.
我们在清场
We're in the clear.
夏延  雷死了
Cheyenne, Ray's dead.
什么
What?
朱尼尔救不了他
Junior couldn't save him.
该死的
God damn it.
朱尼尔  给国土部打电话
Junior, get Homeland on the phone.
你妻子给我打了12个未接电话
I have twelve missed calls from your wife.
没有留言  只有这些电话
No messages, just all these calls.
什么
What?
怎么了
What's goin' on?
他有楚其
He's got Chucky.
你在说什么
What are you, what are you talkin' about?
我有楚其
I do have Chucky.
我还有你妻子
I also have your wife.
她忘了提那件事
She forgot to mention that.
如果你伤害他们  我会
If you harm them, I'll...
你会怎样
You'll what?
叫无人机
Call a drone?
杀了我们所有人
Kill all of us?
就像你对我家人那样
Like you did to my family?
我不知道你到底在说什么
I don't know what the hell you're talkin' about.
告诉你的狼群  还有你那凶残的国安局同伙
Tell your wolves, and your murderous NSA sidekick,
如果他们打一个电话
that if they make a single call,
我要炸掉你妻子的头
I'll blow your wife's head off.
在楚其面前
In front of Chucky.
我是认真的
I mean it!
我在用相机监视你
I'm watching you with my cameras.
嘘
Psst.
你做了什么
What have you done?
死亡来得那么快
Death comes that quick.
从天上发射的东西  一代又一代被消灭
Something fired from the heavens, generations wiped out,
屠杀无辜的孩子
slaughtered innocent children,
把爷爷的头给炸了
blow the heads off of grandfathers.
如果你杀了他们
If you kill them...
你就跑了
And you ran away!
你和你的小狼
You and your little wolves.
那么勇敢  跑回你的圣地
So brave, running back here to your sacred lands.
你以为你很安全
You thought you were safe.
不
No.
勇敢的战士  你的痛苦不会这么快结束
Brave warrior, your pain will not be over so quick.
纳巴  请照他说的做
Nabahe, do what he said, please.
你可以拥有我
You can have me.
让他们走吧
Just let them go.
我从来没有提出过这样的建议
I never got to make such an offer.
清晨  一个村庄沉睡
Early morning, a village sleeps,
不打扰大美洲帝国
not bothering the great American empire.
然后按下一个按钮
Then a button is pushed.
岩石压碎了我母亲的头
Rocks crush the head of my mother,
我每晚亲吻的脸颊
the very cheeks I kissed each night.
你不认为我会乞求你现在做什么
You do not think I would have begged for what you do now?
为了他们我
Me for them?
我支持他们
Me for them!
不
No!
纳巴  嘿  嘿
Nabahe, hey, hey!
纳巴  你得保持清醒
Nabahe, you gotta keep your head.
他还没杀他们
He hasn't killed 'em yet.
他只是在争取时间
He's just buyin' time.
我们得给祖国打电话
We gotta call Homeland.
不  他会杀了他们
No, he will kill them!
他会杀更多的人
Well, he's gonna kill a whole lot more.
这是我们部落的赌场
It's our tribe's casino.
是的  我们现在得找到这个拖车
Yeah, and we gotta find this trailer now.
谁知道他有什么计划
Who knows what he's got planned!
你不会杀了我妻子和女儿的
You're not gonna get my wife and daughter killed.
纳巴  不
Nabahe, no.
什么
What?
你想让我做什么
What do you want me to do?
在你的圣山见我
Meet me at your sacred hill.
你的祖先可以看着你死在那里
Your ancestors can watch you die there.
我会去的
I'll be there.
小家伙  把马送到医院
Junior, get Horse to a hospital.
他说员工停车场有拖车
He says there's a trailer in employee parking.
我们把所有人都救出来
Let's get everyone out.
肖  他们正在疏散赌场
Shaw, they're evacuating the casino now.
很好
Good.
就在那儿
There it is!
来吧  你妻子在这边
Come, your wife is this way.
不  等等  等等  等等  等等  等等  等等  等等
No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
它被操纵了
It's rigged.
可以
Okay.
有人在里面
Someone's in there.
嘿
Hey!
嘿  你能听见我说话吗
Hey, can you hear me?
有个通风口
There's a vent.
嘿  你能听见我说话吗
Hey, can you hear me?
我什么也看不见
I can't see anything.
在这里
Here.
-楚其  -楚其
- Chucky? - Chucky?
楚其  你没事吧
Chucky, are you okay?
楚其  你受伤了吗
Chucky, are you hurt?
你就坐好了  好吗  我们会把你弄出去的
You just sit tight, all right? We're gonna get you outta here.
坚持住
Just hang on.
可以
Okay.
是个炸弹
It's a bomb.
好吧  等等  楚其
All right, hang on, Chucky.
等一下
Hold on a second now.
开枪打我  你的赌场就爆炸了
Shoot me, and your casino blows up.
每个人都会为他们腐朽的狂欢而死
Everybody will be dead at their decadent rave.
不  勇敢的战士
No, brave warrior.
现在没有白人武器能救你了
No white man weapons can save you now.
我在你家发现的
I found these at your home.
所以  选择你的武器
So, choose your weapon.
是的  在我杀了你之后  我会把她活活烧死
And, yes, after I kill you I will burn her alive.
来吧
Come on.
好吧  我马上回来  好吗
Okay, I'm gonna be right back, okay?
坐好
Just sit tight.
听着  你不必这么做
Listen, you don't have to do this.
你为什么不杀了我放了她
Why don't you just kill me and let her go?
不会那么容易的
It's not going to be that easy.
我会杀了你的整个部落就像杀了我的一样
I will kill your whole tribe like you did mine.
我够不着
I can't reach it.
我们能开枪吗
Can we shoot it?
不  它会爆炸的
No, it'll blow.
打电话给祖国
Call Homeland.
你不会得逞的
You are not going to get away with this.
无论如何我都会死的
I'm going to die anyway!
国土至少10分钟
Homeland's 10 minutes at least.
10分钟
10 minutes?
我们只有不到六个
Well, we've got less than six.
这种死没有什么高尚的
There is nothing noble about this death.
但是你  你仍然可以光荣地死去
But you, you could still die with honor,
如果你能把这个拿走
if you can take this away from me.
楚其
Chucky?
嘿  好吧  就这样
Hey, okay, this is gonna be just like one
你的魔术  好吗
of your magic tricks, okay?
坐着别动  好吗
Just sit still right there, okay?
我要把电线冻住
I'm gonna try to freeze the wires.
该死的
Damn it.
我做不到
I can't get to it!
我只是距离不够近
I'm just not close enough.
是你领导了伟大的
You were the one who led the great
以及强大的美国军队
and powerful U.S. Army.
他们来教化我们
They came to civilize us,
以他们自己的形象塑造我们
to make us in their own image
就像他们对待你的人一样
just like they did your people.
该死  不到三分钟  我要开枪了
Damn, there's less than three minutes. I'm gonna shoot.
不  最后一次
No, one last try!
好吧  楚其  楚其
Okay, Chucky, Chucky.
我需要你帮我
I need you to help me.
好吗
All right?
这将是有史以来最好的魔术  好吗
This is gonna be like the best magic trick ever, okay?
我要你拿着这个罐子
I need you to take this can.
拿着罐子  来吧  拿着罐子
Take the can, come on, take the can.
我要你把它倒喷在电线上好吗
And I need you to spray it backwards on those wires okay?
楚其  你能行的
Chucky, you can do this!
为你父母做  好吗
Do it for your mom and your dad, okay?
你能做到的
You can do it.
她在干什么
What's she doing?
我不知道
I don't know.
怎么了
What's goin' on?
-我不知道  -让我看看
- I don't know. - Lemme see.
你以为我只有一种引爆炸弹的方法吗
Did you think I had only one way to set my bomb off?
她只是  啊      楚其
She's just, ah... Chucky!
现在你可以看着死亡降临到你的人民身上
Now you can watch death come to your people.
怎么了  楚其
What's going on, Chucky?
发生什么事
What's going on?
我不明白
I don't understand.
楚其
Chucky!
哦
Oh!
蜂蜜
Honey.
是 啊
Yeah?
纳巴  纳巴
Nabahe, Nabahe!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
是的  是楚其吗
Yeah, is Chucky?
她还活着
She's alive.
她阻止了炸弹
She stopped the bomb.
你在哪里  可汗呢
Where are you? Where's Khan?
就让我  让我  我  让我和她谈谈  好吗
Just lemme, lemme, I, lemme me talk to her, please?
是 啊
Yeah.
给你  亲爱的
Here, honey.
爸爸  我没事
Daddy, I'm okay.
只是几根绳子烧了
It just a couple of rope burns.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
你妈妈来了
I got your mom here.
她也没事
She's okay, too.
纳巴  楚其真勇敢
Nabahe, Chucky was so brave.
她把绳子冻僵以挣脱束缚
She froze the ropes to free herself.
那是我的女孩
That's my girl.
可汗呢
And Khan?
恐怕他现在不能和你说话
I'm afraid he can't talk to you right now.
他胸中有一只战斧
He's got a tomahawk in his chest.
纳巴  你坚持住
Nabahe, you hang in there.
救护车在路上
The ambulance is on the way.
让我跟楚其说再见
Let me say goodbye to Chucky.
当死亡降临时
As death comes to us all,
总是淡季
always outta season.
我打败了杀人犯  肖
I beat the slayer, Shaw.
你也会的
You will too.
楚其  求你了
Chucky, please.
*安静点  小宝贝  现在不要哭了*
* Hush little baby now don't you cry *
*爸爸会给你买只蝴蝶*
* Daddy's gonna buy you a butterfly *
*如果那只蝴蝶不会唱歌*
* And if that butterfly can't sing *
*爸爸会给你买一颗钻石*
* Daddy's gonna buy you a diamond *
是 啊
Yeah?
糟糕的时候
Bad time?
总是不好的时候
It's always a bad time.
我有情况
I've got a situation.
我要你今晚飞出去
I need you flying out tonight.
好吧  但我要带狼来
Okay, but I'm bringing the Wolves.
打得好
Good call.
*我听到毁灭的声音*
* I hear the sound of destruction *
*我闻到了我的光线中断的气味*
* I smell the scent of my light break *
*我在阴影中触摸你的恐惧*
* I touch your fear in the shadow *
*我看着狼挖你的坟墓*
* I watch the wolves dig up your grave *
*我的灵魂在月光下狩猎*
* My spirit hunts in the moonlight *
*我感觉到你在沙滩上留下的痕迹*
* I feel your tracks in the sand *
*你假装没看见我*
* You pretend you don't see me *
*我看到你手上的血迹*
* I see the blood stains on your hands *
*猎影狼*
* Shadow wolves on the hunt *
*扔掉你不能穿过的泥土*
* Throwin' the dirt where you will not cross *
*烈火呼喊*
* Spirits of fire shout *
*很快你就会报复你的上帝*
* Soon you'll revenge your god *
*猎影狼*
* Shadow wolves on the hunt *
*扔掉你不能穿过的泥土*
* Throwin' the dirt where you will not cross *
*烈火呼喊*
* Spirits of fire shout *
*很快你就会报复你的上帝*
* Soon you'll revenge your god *
*猎影狼*
* Shadow wolves on the hunt *
*扔掉你不能穿过的泥土*
* Throwin' the dirt where you will not cross *
*烈火呼喊*
* Spirits of fire shout *
*很快你就会报复你的上帝*
* Soon you'll revenge your god *